TAYLOR ATKIN

+1(480)980-4058



taylor58.dev@gmail.com



Rexburg, Idaho



SUMMARY

Highly motivated programmers with experience in various areas. With a focus on Web Development. Over 5+ years of experience in Web Development. Expertise in Back-End, Front-End, and Full-Stack development. I'm highly motivated to discover new concepts, techniques, and new technologies. I have experience with React, NodeJs, JavaScript, HTML, CSS and more. I have experience in various areas of technology and I am excited and motivated to perform professional grade work that employers will desire.

EDUCATION

Programmer

Brigham Young University - Idaho

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2022 - Summer 2023

Northern Arizona University

Bachelor's Degree In Computer Science 2020 – 2022

SKILLS

- Strong understanding of Web Development
- · Clean coding with comments
- Reports of programming and updates
- Experience with various databases
- Experience with REST APIs
- Strong understanding and implementation of ReactJs, NodeJs, and Express
- Understanding of mobile application development.
- · Strong understanding of python

PROGRAMMING

Front-End Development, Back-End Development, Full-Stack Development, ReactJs, NodeJs, Javascript, HTML, CSS, REST APIs, Express, Python, Clojure, Swift, Java, C#, Erlang, PHP, Third-Party API, Google Console, Google Admin Suite, Firebase, MongoDB, MySQL, Mobile Application Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist

Eduprize Schools | May 2023 - August 2023

- 63 times Running and terminating low electric wire
- Install, and maintain 59 Cameras, and install NVR for recording
- · Maintaining servers and infrastructure
- Domain switch of network
- Maintaining Chromebook distribution and maintenance (400+) distributed in 1 week to students)

Overnight Stocker

Walmart | Sep 2022 - May 2023

- Keep track of inventory and stock shelves
- · Manages customer service and customer satisfaction
- Manage large quantities of freight, stocking and movement (Avg of 1200 cases of freight per night)
- · Oversee cold and frozen food storage and protocols
- Proper disposal of cardboard, plastic, and hazardous material

Maintenance and IT specialist

Eduprize | May 2020 - Sep 2022

- Perform upkeep of the property
 - · Landscaping for an average of 4 hours daily
 - Fulfill tickets (average of 20 per day)
- Running and termination of low electric wire (Approximately 50 lines run)
- Managing Device distribution and maintenance
 - o 400+ devices distributed in one week
 - o Maintaining all devices and performing repairs